[
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da subtração: 17-9?",
        "choice1": "7",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "10",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da subtração: 32-17?",
        "choice1": "14",
        "choice2": "15",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "8",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da subtração: 36-15-8?",
        "choice1": "13",
        "choice2": "15",
        "choice3": "17",
        "choice4": "19",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 9-3?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "4",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 15-13?",
        "choice1": "1",
        "choice2": "3",
        "choice3": "2",
        "choice4": "4",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 58-29?",
        "choice1": "27",
        "choice2": "28",
        "choice3": "29",
        "choice4": "30",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 73-58?",
        "choice1": "15",
        "choice2": "14",
        "choice3": "13",
        "choice4": "12",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 16-7?",
        "choice1": "6",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "9",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 23-6?",
        "choice1": "17",
        "choice2": "15",
        "choice3": "20",
        "choice4": "18",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da subtração: 67-18-32?",
        "choice1": "18",
        "choice2": "27",
        "choice3": "16",
        "choice4": "26",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 5
    }
]